Guide to the Anne Morrow Lindbergh Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings, 1919-1976; Series VII
  - Printed copies of Anne Morrow Lindbergh's work
    - While We Are Absent by Ann Leighton: (review) The Progressive, 1943 Ju1 12 (Box 163, Folder 464)
    - The Steep Ascent, 1944 (Box 164, Folder 465)
    - "My Most Unforgettable Character" (article) Reader's Digest, 1947 January (Box 164, Folder 466)
    - "Songs for Flying" (poems) Atlantic Monthly, 1947 July (Box 164, Folder 467)
    - "All Saints' Day," "The Burning Tree" (poems) Atlantic Monthly, 1947 November (Box 164, Folder 468)
    - "The Flame of Europe" (article) Reader's Digest, 1948 January (Box 164, Folder 469)
    - "One Starts at Zero" (article) Reader's Digest, 1948 February (Box 164, Folder 470)
    - "The Flame of Europe" (article) Reader's Digest
      - Spanish, Norwegian, Danish, Chinese, 1948 March (Box 164, Folder 471)
      - French, 1948 March (Box 164, Folder 472)
      - Finnish, Swedish, 1948 March (Box 165, Folder 473)
    - "One Starts at Zero" (article) Reader's Digest
      - Finnish, Chinese, 1948 March (Box 165, Folder 474)
      - French, 1948 March (Box 165, Folder 475)
      - Spanish, 1948 March (Box 165, Folder 476)
      - Norwegian, 1948 March (Box 165, Folder 477)
    - "Anywhere in Europe" (article) Harper's Monthly, 1948 April (Box 165, Folder 478)
    - "Second Swing" (poems) Atlantic Monthly, 1948 August (Box 165, Folder 479)
    - "Airliner to Europe" (article) Harper's Magazine, 1948 September (Box 165, Folder 480)
    - "The Mother and the Child" (article) Harper's Bazaar, 1948 December (Box 165, Folder 481)
    - "Winter Tree" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1950 March (Box 165, Folder 482)
    - "Our Lady of Risk" (article) Life, 1950 July (Box 166, Folder 483)
    - "At the Abbey of Our Lady of Risk" (article) Catholic Digest, 1950 October (Box 166, Folder 484)
    - "J'ai trouvé réponse à vos angoisses" (article) Ecclesia, 1956 March (Box 166, Folder 484)
    - "The Man and the Child" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1951 February (Box 166, Folder 485)
    - "Within the Wave" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1951 October (Box 166, Folder 486)
    - "Space" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1951 November (Box 166, Folder 487)
    - "The Stone" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1952 January (Box 166, Folder 488)
    - "A Leaf, a Flower, and a Stone" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1952 October (Box 166, Folder 489)
    - "Broken Shell" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1954 January (Box 166, Folder 490)
    - "Back to the Islands" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1954 March (Box 166, Folder 491)
    - Gift from the Sea, 1955 (Box 166, Folder 492)
    - "Three Shells," selection from Gift from the Sea in Harper's Bazaar, 1955 January (Box 166, Folder 493)
    - Gift from the Sea
      - Book condensation in Reader's Digest, 1955 May (Box 167, Folder 494)
      - Book condensation in Reader's Digest, 1955 September (Box 167, Folder 495)
        - Spanish, 1955 August (Box 167, Folder 496)
        - Chinese, Portuguese, 1955 September (Box 167, Folder 497)
        - Danish, Spanish, 1955 October-November (Box 167, Folder 498)
    - "Bare Tree" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1955 March (Box 167, Folder 499)
    - The Unicorn and Other Poems, 1956 September 15 (Box 167, Folder 500)
    - "Revisitation" (poem) Vogue, 1956 September 15 (Box 167, Folder 501)
    - "Mid-Summer" (poem) Atlantic Monthly, 1957 December (Box 167, Folder 502)
    - Dearly Beloved (English, German), 1962, 1978 (Box 167, Folder 503)
    - Dearly Beloved selection in McCalls, 1962 May (Box 168, Folder 504)
    - "As I See Our First Lady," (article) Look, 1964 May 19 (Box 168, Folder 505)
    - "A Safari Back to Innocence" (article) Life, 1966 October 21 (Box 168, Folder 506)
      - Condensation in Reader's Digest (German), 1967 April (Box 168, Folder 506)
    - "Discovery and Renewal" (article) Reader's Digest, 1967 June (Box 168, Folder 507)
    - "The Heron and the Astronaut" (article) Life, 1969 February 28 (Box 168, Folder 508)
    - Earth Shine, 1969 (Box 168, Folder 509)
    - "Earth Values" (address) Smith Alumnae Quarterly, 1970 April (Box 168, Folder 510)
    - "Harmony with the Life around Us" (article) Good Housekeeping, 1970 July (Box 168, Folder 511)
    - Images and Shadows by Iris Origo, (review) The American Scholar, 1971 winter (Box 168, Folder 512)
    - Bring Me a Unicorn, 1972 (Box 168, Folder 513)
      Diaries and letters
    - Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead, 1973, 1976 (Box 169, Folder 514-514a)
      Diaries and letters (English, German, and Japanese)
  - Reviews and notices of Anne Morrow Lindbergh's work
    - Bring Me a Unicorn, 1972 (Box 169, Folder 515-516)
    - Dearly Beloved, 1962 (Box 169, Folder 517)
    - Earth Shine, 1969 (Box 169, Folder 518)
    - Gift from the Sea, 1955 (Box 169, Folder 519)
    - Hour of Gold, Hour of Lead, 1973 (Box 169, Folder 520)
    - Listen! The Wind, 1938 (Box 169, Folder 521-523)
    - Listen! The Wind, 1938 (Box 170, Folder 524)
    - North to the Orient, 1935 (Box 170, Folder 525-533)
    - Le Monde vu de haut, 1935 (Box 170, Folder 534)
    - The Steep Ascent, 1944 (Box 170, Folder 535)
    - The Wave of the Future, 1941 (Box 170, Folder 536)
- Housekeeping and social records, 1927-1974; Series VIII
  The series are arranged by genre, and chronologically within genre.
  The series includes engagement calendars and notes; address books and lists; planning materials for family vacations and Christmas celebrations; bills and receipts for routine household expenditures; advertisements for household furnishings and clothing saved by Lindbergh; and various business and financial records.
  - Engagement calendars and notes
    Materials in this subseries are arranged only by year, not by month.
    - 1927-1937 (Box 171, Folder 1-13)
    - 1937-1940 (Box 172, Folder 14-23)
    - 1940-1944 (Box 173, Folder 24-34)
    - 1944-1948 (Box 174, Folder 35-43)
    - 1949-1956 (Box 175, Folder 44-52)
    - 1957-1962 (Box 176, Folder 53-64)
    - 1962, 1964, 1966, 1970-1971, undated (Box 177, Folder 65-69a)
  - Address books and lists
    - 1929-1936 (Box 177, Folder 70-73)
    - 1937-1955 (Box 178, Folder 74-83)
    - 1947-1964, undated (Box 179, Folder 84-93)
  - Licenses, passports, and identification cards
    - 1928-1959 (Box 179, Folder 94-96)
    - 1936-1972 (Box 180, Folder 97-100)
  - Christmas
    - 1932-circa 1936, 1940-1944 (Box 180, Folder 101-108)
    - 1944-1954 (Box 181, Folder 109-123)
    - 1954-1958, undated (Box 182, Folder 124-132)
  - Vacation materials
    - 1931-1933, 1944, 1947 (Box 182, Folder 133-137)
    - 1948-1950, 1952-1960 (Box 183, Folder 138-153)
    - 1961-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 184, Folder 154-160)
  - Advertisements
    - 1929, 1931-1936 (Box 184, Folder 161-170)
    - 1937-1944 (Box 185, Folder 171-184)
    - 1944-1945, 1947, 1953-1955, 1958-1959, undated (Box 186, Folder 185-198)
  - Miscellaneous housekeeping materials
    - Houses: Martha's Vineyard, 1941-1942 (Box 187, Folder 199)
    - Houses: Bloomfield Hills, 1942 (Box 187, Folder 200)
    - Apartments in New York City, 1934 (Box 187, Folder 201)
    - Household and clerical employees, 1932-1938, 1952-1955, 1959-1972 (Box 187, Folder 202-207)
    - Dogs: Gubbio, 1947-1948 (Box 187, Folder 208)
    - Dogs: Brenna, Heather, and Devin, 1963-1970 (Box 187, Folder 209)
  - Business and financial records
    - Bank books, 1930, 1958-1960 (Box 187, Folder 210-211)
    - Bank stubs, 1934-1943 (Box 187, Folder 212)
    - Bills and receipts
      - 1931 (Box 187, Folder 213)
      - 1932-1940 (Box 188, Folder 214-232)
      - 1941-1962 (Box 189, Folder 233-251)
      - 1962-1970 (Box 190, Folder 252-263)
    - Business firms: correspondence
      - 1929-1934 (Box 190, Folder 264-269)
      - 1935-1946 (Box 191, Folder 270-291)
      - 1946-1970 (Box 192, Folder 292-308)
    - Contributions
      - 1936-1966 (Box 192, Folder 309-323)
      - 1967-1974 (Box 193, Folder 324-332)
- Institutions, committees, and clubs, 1934-1973; Series IX; The series is arranged alphabetically by name of organization.
  The series includes correspondence, annual reports, and memoranda from philanthropic, educational, cultural, and social groups and organizations in which Lindbergh took an active interest or served as a board member. Of particular interest to her were the Elisabeth Morrow School, established by her sister and supported by the family after her death; Food and Parcels for Europe that aided needy families in post-war Europe; and the Institute of Direct Analysis.
  - American Friends Service Committee
    - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, bulletins, reports, 1941 (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, bulletin, 1942 (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, annual reports, 1943-1946 (Box 194, Folder 5-7)
    - Correspondence, bulletin, annual report, 1947 (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, bulletin, 1948 (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Chapin School Alumni Association, 1936-1964 (Box 194, Folder 10)
  - Children's Medical Relief International, Inc. correspondence, 1971 (Box 194, Folder 11)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, 1946-1968 (Box 194, Folder 12-13)
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1943-1944 (Box 194, Folder 14)
    See also: Correspondence with friends and acquaintances, Series I, Milles, Carl, box 14, folder 291
  - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1944-1968 (Box 195, Folder 15)
  - Elisabeth Morrow School
    - Correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 195, Folder 16)
    - Budget and agenda for board of trustees' meetings, 1948 (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Budget and agenda for board of trustees' meetings and Elisabeth Reeve Morrow Morgan Foundation, 1949-1953 (Box 195, Folder 18)
    - Budget and correspondence regarding last will of Elizabeth C. Morrow, 1954-1955 (Box 195, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence regarding Elisabeth Reeve Morrow Morgan Foundation and school expansion plan, 1955-1956 (Box 195, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, agenda, and budget, 1957 (Box 195, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, financial statements, and "Analysis of Needs and Plans for Future Development", 1958-1959 (Box 195, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, financial statements, 1960 (Box 195, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, financial statements, minutes of meetings, and Three School Development Council, 1961 (Box 195, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, agenda, Three School Development Foundation, Inc., and address to graduating class by Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1962 (Box 195, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Three School Development Foundation, Inc., 1963 (Box 196, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: financial material, and Three School Development Foundation, Inc., 1964 (Box 196, Folder 27)
    - Financial material, and minutes of meetings, 1965-1966 (Box 196, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, agenda and minutes of meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 196, Folder 29)
    - Minutes and agenda of meetings, and financial statements, 1969 (Box 196, Folder 30)
    - EMS bulletin and Three School Development Foundation, Inc., 1970 (Box 196, Folder 31)
    - Minutes, agenda and financial statements, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 32)
    - Minutes of meetings and Three School Development Foundation, Inc., 1972 (Box 196, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence re: Dedication of Chilton House by Anne Morrow Lindbergh, and financial statements, 1972 (Box 196, Folder 34)
    - Minutes of meetings and Three School Development Foundation, Inc., 1973 (Box 197, Folder 35)
  - Food and Parcels to Europe
    - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 197, Folder 36-38)
    - Printed material, 1947-1949 (Box 197, Folder 39)
  - Food for the Small Democracies
    - Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 197, Folder 40-41)
    - Printed material, 1941 (Box 197, Folder 42-43)
    - Correspondence, printed material, 1943 (Box 197, Folder 44)
      See also: Herbert Hoover series I, box 9, folder 183
  - Institute for Direct Analysis
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 45-46)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 47)
    - Report to Rockefeller Brothers' Fund, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, reports and minutes, 1956 (Box 198, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, reports and financial material, 1956 (Box 198, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1957 (Box 198, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, reports and memoranda, 1957 (Box 198, Folder 52-53)
    - Correspondence, reports and financial material, 1958 (Box 198, Folder 54-55)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1959 (Box 198, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1960 (Box 198, Folder 57)
      See also: Correspondence from friends and acquaintances, Series I, Rosen, John, box 20, folder 388
  - The Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 1971 (Box 198, Folder 58)
    Correspondence and statement by Anne Morrow Lindbergh
  - Moral Re-Armament
    - "The World News", 1945-1946 (Box 198, Folder 59)
    - Programs, 1947 (Box 198, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 198, Folder 61)
    - Material from National and World Assembly for MRA, 1951 (Box 198, Folder 62)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1934-1969 (Box 199, Folder 63-64)
    Correspondence and bulletins
  - National Geographic Society, 1934 (Box 199, Folder 65)
    Correspondence and presentation speech
  - Poetry Society of America, 1939-1964 (Box 199, Folder 66)
    Correspondence and membership cards
  - Smith College
    - Correspondence of alumnae material, 1937-1942 (Box 199, Folder 67)
    - Correspondence and fifteenth reunion material, 1943-1947 (Box 199, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence and twentieth reunion material, 1948-1949 (Box 199, Folder 69)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 199, Folder 70)
    - Correspondence and reunion news, 1953-1955 (Box 199, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1956-1959 (Box 199, Folder 72)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 199, Folder 73)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1965-1970 (Box 199, Folder 74)
    - Correspondence and Smith Alumnae Quarterly, 1971-1973 (Box 199, Folder 75)
- Childhood, school, and college, 1912-1928; Series X
  Materials in the series are arranged chronologically by educational institution.
  The series consists of student work, notes, report cards, and memorabilia documenting Lindbergh's school years. At the end of the series there are several collections kept by Lindbergh including Christmas cards, postcards, theater programs, and pictures.
  - Dwight School, 1912-1919
    - Themes and notebooks (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Report cards (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Entertainment programs (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Artwork (Box 211B)
  - Miss Chapin's School, 1919-1924
    - Class notes (Box 200, Folder 4-5)
    - Essays and themes (Box 200, Folder 6-10)
    - Examinations (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - Report cards (Box 201, Folder 12-13)
    - Poems copied by Anne Morrow Lindbergh (Box 201, Folder 14-15)
    - Autograph books (Box 201, Folder 16)
    - Invitations and engagements (Box 201, Folder 17)
    - Class songs and poems (Box 201, Folder 18)
    - Club notices and minutes (Box 201, Folder 19)
    - Diploma, 1924 (Box 211A)
    - Artwork (Box 211B)
    - Entertainment and exhibition programs (Box 201, Folder 20)
  - Smith College, 1924-1928
    - Student directories (Box 202, Folder 21)
    - Student handbook (Box 202, Folder 22)
    - Invitations and engagements (Box 202, Folder 23-24)
    - Theatre and concert programs (Box 202, Folder 25-27)
    - Financial records - cancelled checks and receipts (Box 202, Folder 28)
    - Membership cards and memorabilia (Box 202, Folder 29)
    - Examinations (Box 202, Folder 30-31)
    - Report cards (Box 202, Folder 32)
    - Essays and themes (Box 203, Folder 33-36)
    - Lecture notes (Box 203, Folder 37-43)
    - Lecture notes (Box 204, Folder 44-54)
    - Lecture notes (Box 205, Folder 55-62)
    - Lecture notes (Box 206, Folder 63-69)
    - Lecture notes (Box 207, Folder 70-75)
    - Lecture notes (Box 208, Folder 76-78A)
    - Artwork (Box 211B)
    - Diplomas, 1928, 1935 (Box 211B)
      Includes two honorary degrees granted in 1939 by Amherst College and the University of Rochester.
  - Card, program, and picture collections
    - Christmas card collection (Box 208, Folder 79-84)
    - Postcard collection (Box 209, Folder 85-92)
    - Theatre program collection (Box 209, Folder 93-94)
    - Theatre program collection (Box 210, Folder 95-97)
    - Picture collection (Box 210, Folder 98-100)
    - Valentine card collection (Box 210, Folder 101)
    - Gift card collection (Box 210, Folder 102)
    - Calendar collection (Box 210, Folder 103)
- Memorabilia, 1920s-1970s; Seies XI
  The series consists of a miscellany of artifacts, memorabilia, and articles and clippings about Anne Morrow Lindbergh.
  - Embroidered handkerchiefs sent to Anne Morrow Lindbergh by admirers, Undated (Box 211, Folder 1)
  - Crocheted doily depicting Spirit of St. Louis, Undated (Box 211, Folder 2)
  - We Are to Blame - handbound edition sent by the author (Box 211, Folder 3)
  - Embroidered purse made by Greek refugees, [1947?] (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Invitation and menu from White House dinner, 1972 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Dance book from Junior Promenade, Class of 1928, Yale University, Circa 1927 (Box 211, Folder 6)
  - Drawing of Holstenberg by Commander Dan, 1933 (Box 211, Folder 7)
  - National Aeronautic Association of the United States of America - certificate, 1922 (Box 211, Folder 8)
  - National Audubon Society - certificate, 1971 (Box 211, Folder 9)
  - Pan American Airways - certificate, 1959 (Box 211, Folder 10)
  - St. Nicholas League - certificate, Undated (Box 211A)
  - Articles and clippings regarding Anne Morrow Lindbergh, 1920s-1970s (Box 211, Folder 11-18)
- 1980 Addition, 1957-1976; 1974-1976
  The addition is arranged in ten sections: Correspondence from friends and acquaintances; Family correspondence and records; Correspondence with publishers: General correspondence; Correspondence from readers; Outgoing correspondence; Writings; Houskeeping and social records; Institutions, committees, and clubs; and Memorabilia.
  Headings in the addition correspond to titles of series from the main accession. In all of the correspondence, missing dates and names have been transcribed from the envelopes. Lindbergh annotated some letters "RU" for "request unanswered." Others are marked "Answer" or "To be answered," but Outgoing correspondence does not contain responses to all of these letters. The addition reflects the wide range of Lindbergh's activities and contacts in the period 1973-1976, but more than half concerns the death of her husband, Charles, in 1974. There are many sympathy cards and letters of condolence.
  - Correspondence from friends and acquaintances
    - Allen, Helen, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Ames, Evelyn, 1974-1975, undated (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Armstrong, Mrs. Hamilton Fish, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Atchley, Dana, 1973-1975 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Atchley, Mary, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Atchley, William Ames, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1974 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Chamberlain, Ernestine (Stodelle), 1974-1975, undated (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Curtiss, Mina (Kirstein), 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Damon, Jean (Shields), 1974 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Delafield, Mary (Walker), 1972-1975 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Delattre, Yvonne, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Edmundson, D'arcy, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Gilder, Comfort, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Harris, Louisa, 1974-1975, undated (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Hatt, Sue (Vaillant), 1973-1975 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Huber, Jack, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Hunter-Gray, Nancy (de Selincourt), 1971 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Jackman, Libby (Sterling), Undated (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Jay, Anne, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Junken, Elizabeth, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Kennedy, Jacqueline
      See: Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, box 212, folder 16
    - Knobel, Elsie, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Lamont, Corliss, 1973-1975 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Lamont, Helen (Lamb), 1974 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Lewis, Dorothy, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - McGavin, Ann, 1975 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - MacGregor, Robert, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Mathias, Sir Richard, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Millar, Margaret (Bartlett) "Monte", 1974 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Mitchell, Stephen, 1973-1975 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Moreillon, Eglantine, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Newton, Eleanor (Forde), 1975 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Newton, James Draper, 1975-1976 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Nicolson, Nigel, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Norris, Marta (Brodie), 1974 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Oldrin, John, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Orteig, Raymond, J., 1974 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Pryor, Mary Tay, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Read, David, 1975 (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Regina Laudis Monastery, 1973-1976 (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Rodewald, Elizabeth (Bacon), 1974 (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Rosen, Hazel, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Rosen, John, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Ross, Nancy Wilson, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Saunders, Jean, 1972-1975, undated (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - Savina, Joseph, 1973-1974 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Scaravelli, Vanda, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Shannon, Mary, 1974-1975 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Sikorsky, Elizabeth, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Katherine, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Speidel, Hans, 1974 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Stirling, Monica, 1973-1976 (Box 213, Folder 22-23)
    - Stuart, Barbara, 1972-1975 (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Sturm, Marthe, 1973, undated (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Swanson, Minnie, 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Taquey, Kitty (McVitty), 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - Trask, Elsie (Barber), 1974 (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - Trask, John J., 1974 (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - Trippe, Betty, 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - Valentine, Alan, 1974-1976 (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - Valentine, Lucia (Norton), 1973-1975 (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - Van Dusen, Elizabeth and Henry Pitney, 1975 (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - Webster, Jean, 1972 (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - Wolff, Helen, 1973-1975 (Box 213, Folder 27)
  - Family correspondence and records
    - Brown, Marjory W., 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Feydy, Hélène, 1974-1976 (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Fulenwider, Constance (Morrow), 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Kenny, Susan (McIlvaine), 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Leighton, Katherine (McIlvaine), 1974 (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow), 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 29)
    - Lindbergh, Anne Spencer, 1974-1975, undated (Box 213, Folder 30-31)
    - Lindbergh, Barbara (Robbins), 1975, undated (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - Lindbergh, Charles, Undated (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - Lindbergh, Erik, 1974-1976 (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - Lindbergh, Kristine, 1975-1976, undated (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - Lindbergh, Leif, 1975 (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - Lindbergh, Lizzie, Undated (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - Lindbergh, Morgan, 1975, undated (Box 213, Folder 32)
    - Lindbergh, Reeve Morrow, 1974-1975, undated (Box 213, Folder 33)
    - Lindbergh, Scott Morrow, 1974-1975 (Box 213, Folder 34)
    - Morgan, Aubrey Niel, 1975 (Box 213, Folder 34)
    - Morgan, Constance (Morrow), 1974-1976, undated (Box 213, Folder 35)
    - Morgan, Dwight Whitney, Jr., 1974-1975 (Box 214, Folder 36)
    - Morgan, Margot (Loines), 1974-1975, undated (Box 214, Folder 36)
    - Morgan, Nancy Lofton, 1974-1975 (Box 214, Folder 37)
    - Pendleton, Elisabeth (Morgan), 1974 (Box 214, Folder 38)
    - Scandrett, Mary (Landenberger), 1973-1974 (Box 214, Folder 38)
    - Vogel, Wendy (Robbins), 1974 (Box 214, Folder 38)